Register of the Commonwealth Club of California records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Sound Recordings of Club Programs, 1944-2004 (Boxes 778-1159, 1191-1240 and on shelf)
  - 1/4-inch sound tape reels (10-inch), 1968-1999
    - 1989 August 25 - 1989 November 9 (Box 1206)
    - 1989 November 9 - 1990 January 26 (Box 1207)
    - 1990 February 1 - 1990 March 14 (Box 1208)
    - 1990 March 16 - 1990 May 22 (Box 1209)
    - 1990 May 23 - 1990 July 20 (Box 1210)
    - 1990 July 24 - 1990 October 19 (Box 1211)
    - 1990 October 26 - 1991 March 8 (Box 1212)
    - 1991 March 12 - 1991 May 23 (Box 1213)
    - 1991 June 3 - 1991 September 30 (Box 1214)
    - 1991 October 2 - 1992 January 31 (Box 1215)
    - 1992 January 31 - 1992 May 20 (Box 1216)
    - 1992 May 22 - 1992 August 24 (Box 1217)
    - 1992 August 28 - 1992 December 11 (Box 1218)
    - 1992 December 11 - 1993 March 26 (Box 1219)
    - 1993 March 26 - 1993 June 11 (Box 1220)
    - 1993 June 16 - 1993 October 8 (Box 1221)
    - 1993 October 13 - 1994 February 9 (Box 1222)
    - 1994 February 10 - 1994 June 3 (Box 1223)
    - 1994 June 10 - 1995 February 24 (Box 1224)
    - 1994 October 14 - 1995 February 24 (Box 1225)
    - 1995 March 3 - 1995 June 21 (Box 1226)
    - 1995 June 23 - 1995 October 20 (Box 1227)
    - 1995 October 24 - 1996 March 14 (Box 1228)
    - 1996 March 22 - 1996 July 24 (Box 1229)
    - 1996 July 26 - 1996 December 5 (Box 1230)
    - 1996 December 6 - 1997 April 4 (Box 1231)
    - 1997 April 16 - 1997 August 4 (Box 1232)
    - 1997 August 22 - 1998 November 22 (Box 1233)
    - 1998 January 23 - 1998 July 15 (Box 1234)
    - 1999 January 13 - undated (Box 1235)
    - 1988 October 10 - undated (Box 1236)
    - 1981 November - 1990 April 6 (Box 1237)
    - Various (Box 1238)
  - Digital audio tapes (DATs)
    - 1945 December 21 - 1972 May 14 (Box 1086)
      Selected programs digitized and restored by the club.
    - 1972 September 8 - 2001 May 2 (Box 1087)
    - 1990 August 10 -1991 January 9 (Box 1088)
    - 1991 January 15 - April 25 (Box 1089)
    - 1991 May 3 - November 22 (Box 1090)
    - 1992 January 17 - 1992 September 11 (Box 1091)
    - 1992 September 18 - 1983 February 10 (Box 1092)
    - 1993 February 19 - May 20 (Box 1093)
    - 1993 May 21 - October 5 (Box 1094)
    - 1993 October 8 - 1994 February 11 (Box 1095)
    - 1994 February 16 - August 19 (Box 1096)
    - 1994 August 25 - 1995 March 10 (Box 1097)
    - 1995 March 6 - July 27 (Box 1098)
    - 1995 August 8 - October 10 (Box 1099)
    - 1995 October 30 - 1996 February 23 (Box 1100)
    - 1996 February 23 - June 7 (Box 1101)
    - 1996 June 14 - September 26 (Box 1102)
    - 1996 September 27 - 1997 February 6 (Box 1103)
    - 1997 February 2 - 1997 May 6 (Box 1104)
    - 1997 May 15 - June 21 (Box 1105)
    - 1997 June 22 - November 6 (Box 1106)
    - 1997 November 11- March 9 (Box 1107)
    - 1998 March 12 - June 25 (Box 1108)
    - 1998 June 26 - November 2 (Box 1109)
    - 1998 November 5 - 1999 March 17 (Box 1110)
    - 1999 April 2 - August 25 (Box 1111)
    - 1999 August 26 - December 1 (Box 1112)
    - 1999 December 2 - 2000 March 27 (Box 1113)
    - 2000 March 30 - June 27 (Box 1114)
    - 2000 June 6 - October 26 (Box 1115)
    - 2000 October 2 - 2001 February 8 (Box 1116)
      Includes some unidentified tapes.
    - 2001 February 21 - May 23 (Box 1117)
    - 2001 May 30 - September 5 (Box 1118)
    - 2001 September 6 - November 12 (Box 1119)
    - 2001 November 13 -2002 March 15 (Box 1120)
    - 2002 March 14 - May 23 (Box 1121)
    - 2002 June 4 - September 18 (Box 1122)
    - 2002 September 23 - November 22 (Box 1123)
    - 2002 December 2 - 2003 April 28 (Box 1124)
      See also Box 1175
    - 2003 April 29 - June 18 (Box 1125)
    - 2003 June 20 - August 28 (Box 1126)
    - 2003 September 4 - October 10 (Box 1127)
    - 2003 October 12 - November 23 (Box 1128)
    - 2003 December 10- 2004 February 11 (Box 1129)
    - 2004 February 11 - April 20 (Box 1130)
    - 2004 April 20 - June 15 (Box 1131)
    - 2004 June 15 - August 30 (Box 1132)
    - 2004 September 7 - November 4 (Box 1133)
    - 2004 November 8 - December 15 (Box 1134)
  - Compact sound discs
    - 1945 December 21 - 2001 May 2 (Box 1135)
    - 1996 August 16 - 1999 September 16 (Box 1136)
    - 1999 September 28 - 2000 November 10 (Box 1137)
    - 2000 September 13 - 2001 May 2 (Box 1138)
    - A Century of Illuminating Important Ideas: Recordings from the Commonwealth Club of California, circa 2003 (Box 1138)
  - Lacquer sound discs
    - 1944-1945 (discs 1-7) (Box 1139)
    - 1945 (discs 8-14) (Box 1140)
    - 1945 (discs 15-20) (Box 1141)
    - 1945-1946 (discs 21-25) (Box 1142)
    - 1945-1946 (discs 26-30) (Box 1143)
    - 1946 (discs 31-35) (Box 1144)
    - 1946 (discs 36-38B) (Box 1145)
    - 1946-1947 (discs 38C-42) (Box 1146)
    - 1947 (discs 43-47) (Box 1147)
    - 1947-1948 (discs 48-50) (Box 1148)
    - 1948 (discs 51-58) (Box 1149)
    - 1948 (discs 59-65) (Box 1150)
    - 1949 (discs 66-73) (Box 1151)
    - 1949-1950 (discs 74-81) (Box 1152)
    - 1950 (discs 82-87) (Box 1153)
    - 1950 (discs 88-93) (Box 1154)
    - 1950-1952 (discs 94-99) (Box 1155)
    - 1952 (discs 100-105) (Box 1156)
    - 1953 (discs 106-109) (Box 1157)
    - 1953 (discs 110-116) (Box 1158)
    - US Army Forces Pacific Area Command special Christmas program, undated (Box 1159)
  - Broken 16-inch lacquer discs
    Access
    Boxes 1239 and 1240 are closed.
    - CLOSED, 1944 March 31, April 28, May 26; 1945 November 16 (Box 1239)
    - CLOSED, 1944 March 3, 1946 February 15 (Box 1240)
- Incremental Material, 1915-2012 (Boxes 1160-1190)
  Sound recordings of club programs, club publications, clippings, commemorative medal, programs, and material concerning proposed speakers, received since the initial acquisition.
  - Sound recordings of club programs (compact sound cassettes)
    - 1987 July 2 - 1988 November 18 (Box 1160)
    - 1988 November 22 - 1989 July 14 (Box 1161)
    - 1989 July 17 - 1990 October 1 (Box 1162)
    - 1990 October 2 - 1990 December 14 (Box 1163)
    - 1991 January 9 - 1993 April 2 (Box 1164)
    - 1993 April 9 - 1993 September 28 (Box 1165)
    - 1993 October 1 - 1994 March 23 (Box 1166)
    - 1991 May 25 - 2000 April 6 (Box 1167)
    - Untitled, unidentified (Boxes 1168-1169)
  - Clippings concerning study sections, 1929-1931 (Box-folder 1170: 1-8)
  - Commemorative medal, Pan-Pacific International Exposition, 1915 June 5 (Box-folder 1170: 9)
  - "At Today's Speaker's Table" program, 1982-1983, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 1171: 1-9)
  - "At Today's Speaker's Table" program, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 1172: 1-2)
  - Referrals (proposed speakers), 1988-1994 (Box-folder 1172: 3-6, 1173: 1-6, 1174: 1-2)
  - The Commonwealth (volumes 65-66), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 1174: 3-4)
  - Sound recordings of club programs (DATs), 2003 February 12 - 2003 March 12 (Box 1175)
  - Sound recordings of club programs (compact sound cassettes)
    - 1959 June 11 - 2000 April 26 (Box 1176)
    - 2000 May 1 - 2000 September 21 (Box 1177)
    - 2000 October 3 - 2001 February 8 (Box 1178)
    - 2001 February 16 - 2001 May 15 (Box 1179)
    - 2001 May 22 - 2001 October 18 (Box 1180)
    - 2001 October 22 - 2002 February 5 (Box 1181)
    - 2001 September 9 - 2001 November 18 (Box 1182)
    - 2002 February 11 - 2002 May 30 (Box 1183)
    - 2002 May 2 - 2002 ugust 15 (Box 1184)
    - 2002 November 19 - 2005 October 25 (Box 1185)
  - Sound recordings of club programs (DATs)
    - 1991 December 6 - 1999 (Box 1185)
    - 2004 January 19 - 2005 February 2 (Box 1186)
    - 2005 February 25 - 2005 April 8 (Box 1187)
    - 2005 April 11 - 2005 November 15 (Box 1188)
  - Sound recordings of club programs (compact sound cassettes), 2005 May 5 - 2005 October 24 (Box 1188)
  - Sound recordings of club programs (MiniDisc), 2002 October 24 (Box 1188)
  - Sound recordings of club programs (compact sound discs), 1995 January - 2002 March 27 (Box 1189)
  - Sound recordings of club programs (compact sound discs), 2002 April 10 - 2003 March 5 (Box 1190)
  - Motion picture film depicting Edward F. Adams, E. A. Walcott, and the Luncheon Committee, time: 08:36, 1928; 1 reel of black-and-white motion picture film, 16 mm, circa 150 feet (Film shelf)
    Included is footage of founder Edward F. Adams; E. A. Walcott, first executive secretary; Luncheon Committee chairman Alonzo Grimes McFarland; 1928 Luncheon Committee members Hibberd and Raas. The film contains intertitles.
    Sequence data: Adams seated at desk, talking, smoking, pounding gavel (00:50), Adams in garden (02:15), Walcott in office reading, talking on phone, signing a check (04:40), McFarland (07:20), Luncheon Committee of 1928: Hibberd, McFarland, and Raas at lunch (07:40), Walcott and McFarland conversing (08:10).
  - Sound recordings of club programs (file-based), 2003 May 13 - 2012 December 18; 2706 digital files (Digital files)
    Digital recordings of recent programs continue to be received on a roughly annual basis.